With a little diagram we could see it this way, right?
Legacy systems are a subset within
the brownfield world. If a project started yesterday
possibly under some of the definitions it is not
its legacy, but it could be
this brownfield
we could say because if it started yesterday there might be little.
low code
including the legacy ones, is that they are in production. If it started yesterday, it is possibly not in production. If it started a month ago, maybe it is, because times have accelerated. At one time one could be with
something for a year without putting it in production. Nowadays times
[sin traducir] tiempos que se manejan, sobre todo con toda la aceleración que
[sin traducir] que nos trae las herramientas de inteligencia
[sin traducir] artificial hace que
that one goes to production much faster.